A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.9-SG 1.13 (A83-A87) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 84), 1963-1984; 1.10; 102.51 Cubic Feet 78 record storage boxes
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - Columbia University - Youth unemployment, 1978-1983 (Box R2200)
      - Jobs for Delaware Graduates, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box R2201)
      - Knodel, John, 1978-1981 1983 (Box R2201)
      - National Commission for Employment Policy - Seminars, 1978-1982 (Box R2201)
      - Northwestern University - Job search, 1979-1980 1982-1983 (Box R2201)
      - Rand Corporation - Malaysia breastfeeding, 1978-1980 1984 (Box R2203)
      - Stanford University - Educational financing study, 1981-1982 (Box R2203)
      - State University of Agric. and Tech. College - Kenyan trainees, 1981-1983 (Box R2203)
      - University of Chicago - Population economics in India, 1977-1982 (Box R2203)
      - University of Wisconsin - Zaire research, 1977-1982 (Box R2203)
      - Yale University - Family households, 1978-1982 (Box R2203)
    - United States - Virus Studies, V
      - Yale University - Pest control viruses, 1974-1983 (Box R2204)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, W
      - Brown University (Schistosomiasis), 1971-1980 1982 (Box R2204)
  - Media Arts Centers, 259
    - Boston Film/Video Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box R2205)
    - Center for New Television, 1980-1983 (Box R2205)
    - Electronic Arts Intermix, 1980-1982 (Box R2205)
    - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video project, 1981-1983 (Box R2205)
    - Southwest Alternate Media Project (SWAMP), 1980-1982 1984 (Box R2205)
    - University Community Video, 1980-1982 (Box R2206)
    - Young Filmmakers Foundation, 1981-1983 (Box R2206)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1980-1983 (Box R2207)
    - Urban Institute - Female youth employment, 1981-1983 (Box R2211)
  - 290
    - (Institute for Policy Research, Inc.), 1978-1984 (Box R2211)
    - (Institute for Policy Research, Inc.) & suppl. material, 1977 (Box R2212)
    - Rocky Mountain Research Institute, 1973-1975 (Box R2212)
    - Rocky Mountain Research Institute supplementary material (Box R2213)
  - Latin America, 300
    - Latin America - Social Sciences, S
      - Latin American Social Sciences Research Council - Population policy - Consultants (A-Z), 1976-1977 (Box R2221)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Andrade, Zilton A., 1982-1983 (Box R2221)
      - Reis, Joao Jose, 1980-1982 (Box R2221)
    - Brazil - Social Sciences, S
      - Brazilian Association for Population Studies, 1976-1982 (Box R2221)
    - Brazil - University Development - Education for Development Program, UD
      Scope and Contents note
      General background on university development in Brazil: i.e. diaries of team visits; overall prospects of RF support; evaluations of progress; Velasquez correspondence (to and from New York) on EFD planning; correspondence with university officials about team visits and RF funding; correspondence and memoranda about overall planning, development and administration of PROPED (program of research and education for development); official letters of request and RF notification of allocations for PROPED support.
      Agricultural Sciences (A 84) — Correspondence and memoranda about AS interests in EFD program; input on development of agronomy faculty at Cruz das Almas. Correspondence to and from Jim Maner, Susan Almy (rural development), Kenneth Buhr and Eugenio Martiner. Diaries of JA Pino visits.
      Health Sciences (A 84) — Correspondence about development of rural and community health projects and Center for the Study of Regional Diseases. Correspondence to and from Willoughby Lathem, Stephen Plank, James Olson. Lathem periodic reports. VC Scott and GS Hayes (NY officers) diaries of visits.
      Social Sciences (A 84) — Correspondence and memoranda about the development of a graduate training program of economics and socio-anthropological studies; correspondence and memos and diaries from A Musalem and Fuenzilidia. Diaries of S Almy. Correspondence and reports on micro economic studies and small business enterprise.
      Administration (A 84) — Correspondence and memoranda on local office administration and administrative matters concerning operations of EFD program center: i.e. routine correspondence about team visits; budget matters; office and vehicle matters; routine personnel matters; fellowship award administration.
      Administration Housing (A 84) — Correspondence, memoranda concerning the purchase or rental of housing for staff assigned to Brazil EFD, including correspondence re utilities and furnishings.
      Agreement (NY) — Correspondence, memoranda and agreements re RF participation in an EFD program in Brazil; privileges extended RF staff by Brazilian government.
      Program Review (A 82) — Program reviews (1974, 1979) by RF officers and 1979 reviews by outside evaluators Sheldon M. Wolff, Arnold C. Harberger and Eduardo L. Venezian.
      Staff Minutes (A 84) — Minutes of meetings held by RF Bahia staff, August 14, 1974 through November 9, 1977
      - (Brazil) (Minutes), 1972-1983 (Box R2138)
      - (and supplementary material), 1963 1965 1967-1971 (Box R2139)
      - Administration, 1977-1984 (Box R2139)
      - Administration, 1972-1976 (Box R2140)
      - Administration - Housing, 1974-1983 (Box R2140)
      - Agricultural Sciences (and supplement files), 1970-1983 (Box R2140)
      - Health Sciences (and supplementary files), 1972-1982 (Box R2141)
      - Social Sciences, 1975-1982 (Box R2141)
      - Social Sciences (and supplement files), 1973-1974 (Box R2142)
      - Staff Minutes, 1974-1977 (Box R2142)
      - University of Bahia - Baseline studies, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Center for Urban Development, 1973 1975 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Community health, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Food production, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Health sciences, 1976-1979 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia [unreadable], 1976 (?) 1981 1983 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Seed storage -, 1982-1983 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia Small farmers, 1976-1979 1982 (Box R2221)
      - University of Bahia - Staff development, 1976-1979 (Box R2222)
  - Chile, 309
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Center for Educational Research and Development (CIDE), 1979-1983 (Box R2222)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Administration, 1967 1971-1979 1981 1983 (Box R2142)
    - Hernandez Garcia, Alberto, 1979-1982 (Box R2222)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Universidad del Valle - Health services, 1970-1977 1979 (Box R2222)
      - Universidad del Valle - Primary health care, 1980-1982 (Box R2222)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Universidad del Valle - Engineering, 1970-1980 1982 (Box R2223)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cano Gallego, Jairo Alonso, 1975-1981 (Box R2223)
      - Florez Nieto, Carmen Elisa, 1979-1983 (Box R2223)
    - Colombia - Population Sciences, P
      - University of the Andes - CLACSO meeting, 1980 (Box R2223)
    - Colombia - Social Sciences, S
      - Colombian Assoc. for the Study of Population - Rural women, 1976-1978 (Box R2223)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, A
      - Metropolitana-Xochimilco University - Workshop, 1981-1982 (Box R2224)
      - National Polytechnic Institute - Liver study, 1980-1984 (Box R2224)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey) (in Arch 2), 1975-1984 1952-1972 (Box R2224)
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey) - Review, 1981-1983 (unreadable) (Box R2224)
      - University of Chapingo - Staff improvement, 1980-1983 (Box R2224)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cortes-Flores, Jose I., 1977-1983 (Box R2224)
      - Maurer Ortiz M., Robert E., 1974-1982 (Box R2224)
      - Ulloa-Aguirre, Alfredo, 1979-1983 (Box R2224)
  - England, 401
    - Minority Rights Group - Haitian Refugees in the United States, 1981-1982 (Box R2224)
    - England - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bridges - webb, C. (Box R2224)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, R
      - British American Arts Association, 1977-1984 (Box R2225)
      - Goldsmiths College - Hologram arts, 1978-1983 (Box R2225)
    - England - Social Sciences, S
      - Institute of Development Studies (Sussex) - Graduate support fund, 1980-1983 (Box R2225)
      - Rweyemamu, Anthony H., 1980-1982 (Box R2225)
  - Australia, 410
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bridges-Webb, Charles, 1981-1982 (Box R2225)
      - University of Western Australia - Strongyloidiasis, 1978-1982 (Box R2225)
  - Canada, 427
    - University of British Columbia - Marine studies, 1978-1981 (Box R2225)
      - Last, John M., 1979-1983 (Box R2225)
      - McMaster University - Clinical epidemiology, 1979-1983 (Box R2225)
      - McMaster University - International workshops, 1979-1981 (Box R2225)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Western Ontario - Demography, 1978-1981 (Box R2226)
  - Grenada/Windward Islands, 455
    - Grenada/Windward Islands - Fellowships, E
      - Long, Earl G. (Box R2226)
  - India, 464
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Ghosh, Maya, 1978-1982 (Box R2226)
      - Nath, Bhola, 1980-1984 (Box R2226)
  - Bengal, 466
    - Bengal - Medical Sciences, A
      - Kabir, Shahjahan, 1980-1982 (Box R2226)
  - France, 500
    - France - Medical Sciences, A
      - Center for Research and Monitoring of Social Conditions, 1979-1982 (Box R2227)
  - China, 601
    - China - Medical Sciences, A
      - Hu, Xaio-su, 1980-1983 (Box R2227)
      - Yuan Hong-chang, 1981 1983 (Box R2227)
      - Zhong Hui-lan, 1981-1982 (Box R2227)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Cao Yung Qing, 1979-1980 (Box R2227)
      - Lin Guo-Wei, 1981-1982 (Box R2227)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Kwon, Tai-Hwan, 1981-1983 (Box R2232)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Bangkok - University development, 1963-1984 (Box R2130)
    - Bangkok - University development (Minutes) (Box R2130)
    - Bangkok - University development (supplementary material (Box R2130)
    - Bangkok - University development - Progress report, 1963-197[?] (Box R2130)
    - Administration, 1970-1983 (Box R2131)
    - Kasetsart University - Donation of equipment, 1971-1983 (Box R2232)
    - Kasetsart University - Panayotou, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2232)
    - Mahidol University - Graduate studies, 1974-1983 (Box R2232)
    - University of Thammasart - Donation of equipment, 1978 (Box R2232)
    - University of Thammasart - Lando, 1978-1983 (Box R2232)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, A
      - Mahidol University - Opisthorchiasis, 1979-1983 (Box R2232)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Bangkok - University development, 1968 1972 (Box R2131)
      - Administration, 1976-1984 (Box R2131)
      - Administration, 1963-1964 1966-1975 (Box R2131)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Boonanan, Chaichalor, 1975-1983 (Box R2233)
      - Boonruksa, Tuisiri, 1978-1981 (Box R2233)
      - Paranee Olarickachard, 1979-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Pinya, Puntipa, 1979-1981 (Box R2233)
      - Preecha, K., 1980-1983 (Box R2233)
      - Preeyanuch Sangpassorn, 1976-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Somkit Tugsinavisuitti, 1976-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Somnuk Tubpun, 1975-1981 (Box R2233)
      - Surin Pitsuwan, 1972-1982 (Box R2233)
      - Tiraporn Bunnag, 1976-1983 (Box R2233)
      - Wilaiwan Wannitikul, 1971-1981 (Box R2233)
    - Thailand - Population Sciences, P
      - Mahidol University - Epididymis-sperm interaction, 1980-1982 (Box R2233)
      - National Institute of Development Administration - Thailand fertility, 1979-1983 (Box R2233, Box R2234)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, S
      - University of Thammasat - Chira, 1981-1982 (Box R2234)
      - University of Thammasat - Economics research project, 1972-1983 (Box R2234)
      - University of Thammasat - Thai Khadi Research Institute, 1978-1982 (Box R2234)
      - University of Thammasat - Thai Khadi Res. Institute - Human rights, 1978-1982 (Box R2234)
  - ICLARM, 626
    - Bailey, L. Conner, Jr., 1978-1983 (Box R2235)
    - Conference, 1973-1974 1978-1979 (Box R2235)
    - Indonesian fisheries, 1980-1983 (Box R2235)
    - International Center for Living Aquatic Resource Management (Box R2235)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Gadjah Mada University - Dove, 1977-1981 (Box R2235)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Darjano, Mr., 1979-1982 (Box R2235)
      - Djamaludin, Ancok, 1975-1983 (Box R2235)
      - Djoko Prajitno, 1977-1981 (Box R2235)
      - Gunawan, Sumofiningrat, 1976-1982 (Box R2235)
      - Hagul, Peter, 1977-1981 (Box R2235)
      - Hari Hartadi, 1976-1981 1983 (Box R2235)
      - Leksono Probo Subanu, 1978-1981 (Box R2236)
      - Nasikun, Mr., 1977-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Rais, Amien, 1974-1981 (Box R2236)
      - Suhargo, Mr., 1980-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Sukanto Reksohadiprodjo, 1975-1981 (Box R2236)
      - Suprodjo Pusposutarjo, 1975-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Tabbu, Charles R., 1978-1982 (Box R2236)
      - Widodo Priyoduprojo, 1978-1982 (Box R2237)
      - Yahya, Muhaimin, 1976-1982 (Box R2237)
    - Indonesia - University Development - Education for Development Program - Gapjah Mada University (GMU), UD
      (overall Program & Policy)
      - General background on university development in Indonesia
      - Diaries of RF officers visiting GMU
      - Correspondence re RF policy on visiting faculty and personnel assigned to GMU
      - Correspondence from A.J. Nyberg re development at GMU
      - Correspondence re external assistance (non RF) to GMU
      - Correspondence re overall faculty development at GMU; overall library development; overall evaluations of allocations; personnel assigned to GMU
      - Program review documents
      - News clippings re social, economic and political developments in Indonesia
      - Program and policy issues at GMU which involve RF role and funding
      - Monthly reports of activities from RF representative, JE Black, 1981-83
      - Final report "EFD - cooperative program, GMU and RF, 1971-83
      Administration
      - Correspondence and memoranda on administrative matters concerning the operation of the EFD program center office, i.e. routine correspondence about officer and team visits (itineraries, travel arrangements, appointments) - to and from RF representative, A.J. Nyberg, and acting representative, R. Northrup
      - Correspondence and notification about bank deposits; audits; budgets and accountings: charges to local EFD center budget (see Note 1 below)
      - Personnel policies for local staff
      - Correspondence about starting at English speaking school in Yogykarta
      - Correspondence with field staff concerning articles and books which are of interest to them
      - Correspondence about the purchase of books and journals for RF staff members
      Note: 1) Correspondence and memoranda related to and charged to items shown in EFD center budget (attached) should be filed in 652 UD - Administration, with the exception of cars and housing.
      2) Correspondence re housing: SEE 652 UD - Gadjah Mada University - Staff Housing
      3) Correspondence re autos: SEE 652 UD - Administration - Automobiles
      Administration Automobiles
      - Correspondence, memoranda concerning purchase and shipment of vehicles for RF staff assigned to GMU
      Agreement
      - Correspondence, memoranda concerning RF agreement with Government of the Republic of Indonesia
      Agricultural Sciences
      - Correspondence and memoranda about AS interests at GMU; with AS field staff assigned to GMU. Correspondence dealing with the establishment and maintenance of relationships with agro complex at GMU
      - General correspondence about RF agricultural sciences fellows from GMU
      - Diaries of RF staff assigned to GMU (Tillman and Thompson, Crowder and Warwick)
      - Reports and papers on AS subjects in relation to curriculum development
      - Occasional "situation" reports vis a vis agro complex at GMU
      - Report by Tillman (December 1980) of seven year experience in EFD at GMU
      Medical Sciences (or Health Sciences)
      - Correspondence, memoranda and diaries of Lucien Gregg and Joe Wray concerning possibilities for an RF role in medicine and health related areas at GMU
      - Correspondence re development of a medical team at GMU
      - Reports of consultants assigned to investigate medical and health departments and facilities at GMU
      - Correspondence and memoranda to and from Jon Rohde and Robert Northrup on medical and health related issues, programs and policies
      - Sundry mimeographed project studies on comprehensive community health, population studies, child health
      Social Sciences
      - Diaries of K.W. Thompson and social science officers concerning an SS role at GMU
      - Correspondence and memoranda to and from D. Hedley and C. MacAndrews on general social science related issues, programs and policies
      - Because of A.J. Nyberg's role as RF representative and economics professor at GMU, 652 UD and 652 UD - Administration should also be consulted for possible social science related correspondence
      - Diaries of D. Hedley and C. MacAndrews
      Allocations and Fellows
      Individual files are maintained for each allocation (see 652 UD - Minutes for mark up) and for each Indonesian fellow (652 E)
      - (Indonesia - University development) (Minutes) (supplementary material), 1967 1969-1983 (Box R2126)
      - Administration, 1972-1984 (Box R2127)
      - Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box R2127)
      - Agricultural Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box R2127)
      - Agricultural Sciences, 1968-1979 (Box R2128)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Computer, 1975-1982 (Box R2237)
      - Gadjah Mada University - English language training, 19[??] (Box R2237)
      - Medical Sciences, 1968-1981 1983 (Box R2129)
      - Program Review, 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box R2129)
      - Program Review (supplementary material), 1979 (Box R2129)
      - Social Sciences, 1968-1971, 1974, 1976-1979 (Box R2129)
  - Greece, 749
    - Greece - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute - Small farmers, 1979-1983 (Box R2238)
  - Norway, 767
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bentsen, Bent Guttorm, 1981-1983 (Box R2238)
  - Portugal, 773
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Pego, Silas E., 1977-1982 1984 (Box R2238)
  - 779
    - 779 - Social Sciences, S
      - Foreign Affairs (Ministry of) - Books, 1977-1982 (Box R2238)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Hazar, Necati, 1979-1982 (Box R2238)
      - Kanbertay, Mesut, 1979-1982 (Box R2238)
      - Kinaci, Engin, 1979-1982 (Box R2238)
    - Turkey - Social Science, S
      - Hacettepe University - Child labor, 1977-1981 (Box R2238)
  - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries, 850
    - (Management Training Programs in Developing Countries), 1976- (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - International Organizations, 103
      - Panafrican Institute for Development - Management training, 1975-1984 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Massachusetts, 224
      - Paul, Samuel, 1978-1982 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Dominican Republic, 335
      - Asociación para el Desarrollo - Agricultural management training, 1978-1981 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Tanzania, 723
      - Eastern and Southern African Management Institute - Women in development, 1981-1983 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Turkey, 805
      - Bogazici University - Agricultural public management, 1977-1983 (Box R2239)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 85), 1970-1985; 1.11; 74.4 Cubic Feet; 62 standard record storage boxes - Box R2242-R2302 and R2304.
  Files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1985.
  - CIAT, 110
    - Blast resistance, 1980-1984 (Box R2242)
  - ICIPE, 117
    - Tick immunology, 1978-1980 (Box R2242)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Adolescent Fertility Regulation - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2242)
    - Antiparasitic Drugs - Conference (also (A 8[? ]), 1982-1984 (Box R2242)
    - Behavioral Epidemiology - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Deterrence Strategy & Psychology - Conference, 1983 (Box R2243)
    - Drama Exchange - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Education for Development Review - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2243)
    - Energy Protein Intake & Activity - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Foreign Debtors Default - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Human Error - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Infection Processes of Fungi - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2243)
    - International Comparison of Cancer-Causing Substances - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - International Network of Food Data Systems - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Italian - American Graduate Education - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Italian Institutions Performance - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Leprosy Research - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R2243)
    - Multinational Enterprises - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - NATO and the Mediterranean - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Nitrogen Fixing Tree Association - Germplasm Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Psychophysiology - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Regional Security Arrangement in the 1980's - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Scholars - Adamolekun, 1981-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Avineri, 1980-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bailyn, B., 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bailyn, L., 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Barrass, 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Barrett, F., 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bateson, 1981-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Beard, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Beck, R., 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bell, D., 1979 1981-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Brief, T., 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bruce-Chwatt, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Cizmar, 1982-1985 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Craddock, 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Davies, 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Del Tredici, 1980 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Desowitz, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Diggins, 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Dolzer, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Dunajewski, 1981-1983 1985 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Elshtain, 1980-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Flaherty, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Frankel, 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Freeman, J., 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Ghent, H. (did not go), 1979-1981 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Godman, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Goldberg, H., 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Haskel, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Heady, 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Horowitz (did not go), 1981-1982 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Humphries (& Barbieri), 1981-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Jackson, W.A.D., 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Jerison, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Jonsen, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)